beautytipshub.com 2017-12-12

# Privacy Policy | Beauty Tips Hub

We at beautytipshub.com are committed to safeguarding your online privacy. Please do read the following policy to understand how your private information will be treated while you make full use of our e-shopping or other offerings. This policy may change from time to time so please come back to check periodically. Beautytipshub.com may collect the information explained herein under.

**1\. What identifiable information is collected from me?**

beautytipshub.com may collect information in one or more ways from different parts of our network of Web sites. beautytipshub.com may ask you for personal information at times, including, but not limited to, when you enter in a contest or promotion sponsored by beautytipshub.com and/or our other contracted partners; and when you report a problem with one of our sites or services. beautytipshub.com occasionally may also ask site user to complete surveys that are use for internal research. Wherever beautytipshub.com collects personal information an effort is made to include a link to this Privacy Policy on that page.

**2\. What are cookies and how beautytipshub.com uses them?**

As combined part of offering and providing customised and personalised services, beautytipshub.com may use cookies to store and track your information. A cookie is a miniscule amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server that may be stored on your computer’s hard drive.

Cache your personalised settings for items such as route language and default country location.Determine whether you are using a public computer so that any beautytipshub.com settings changed while using a public computer do not affect the next user’s ability to use beautytipshub.com . Roughly Estimate our audience or browsers. Each fresh browser trying to access beautytipshub.com may be given a cookie. That maybe used to determine the extent of repeat usage by the user.

Assist us to track the number of visits to and business activities at the beautytipshub.com or beautytipshub.com store, and to track and process the items in your shopping basket.

Track your progress and number of entries or queries in some of our promotions, and contests. When a same hosted promotion uses cookies, the information written to the cookie may be used to track the entries, submissions made, and status in prize drawings list.

Measure certain specific traffic patterns to the site, track the areas of beautytipshub.com network of Web sites visited, track the Web site or geographical location through which you came to beautytipshub.com and your visiting patterns in average. We use this research to understand our users’ visit habits and browsing preferences of if they are similar or different from one another so that we can make each visit by you on beautytipshub.com better experience then last one. We may use this information to better the content, banners, and promotions that you and other users will be likely to see on our sites.

beautytipshub.com also collects geophysical IP addresses for system and server administration and to report visiting information to our advertisers.

Other advertising networks that may serve advertisings onto beautytipshub.com network may also use their own cookies.

beautytipshub.com and its advertisers may also use small pieces of code called ”web beacons” or electronic images that are sometime called “single-pixel GIF” to collect anonymous and average advertising patterns, such as counting hits, browser type, time spent viewing a page, type of page views, promotion views, or advertising responses. These “web beacons” may be used to deliver cookies that conform to our anonymous cookie policy. beautytipshub.com does not allow access or sell other advertisers or their advertising networks, information collected from you.

**3\. Who is collecting information?**

When you are visiting a beautytipshub.com site and are asked for personal information, you are sharing that information for use by beautytipshub.com alone, unless it is specifically stated otherwise. Some beautytipshub.com services may be offered in conjunction with a third partner. In order to provide this service to you, it may be necessary for us to share your personal information with our partner company. In such cases you will be notified prior to the time of the data collection or transfer. Where as if you do not want your data to be shared, you can choose not to allow the transfer of such data by not using that particular service at all.

Sometime promotions that run on beautytipshub.com network sites may be sponsored by companies other than beautytipshub.com or may be co-sponsored by beautytipshub.com and another company. Some or all data collected during such a promotion may be shared with the sponsor. In the event of data being shared, you will be notified prior to the time of data collection or transfer. So you can decide whether to participate in the promotion, if you don’t want your data to be shared.

Please be advised that beautytipshub.com advertisers or Web sites that have links on our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. Such information practices of those Web sites linked to beautytipshub.com are expressly not covered by this privacy statement.

**4\. With who else beautytipshub.com will share my information?**

As a thumb rule, beautytipshub.com will not wilfully disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission or under extraneous circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or under the circumstances described below. Described herein under are some of the ways that your information may be shared or disclosed.

Sponsors & Business Partners: : beautytipshub.com may disclose your personal information to business partners or sponsors, but this is specifically and expressly described to you at the time of data collection or prior to transferring the data. Some or all data collected during a beautytipshub.com promotion may be shared with a sponsor. If a part of personally identifying data about you will be shared, we will tell you before we collect or transfer the data.

During many promotions offers you may be requested for additional information from sponsors. By requesting more information, you give beautytipshub.com permission to transfer your personal information to the sponsor so they can fulfil your request. In majority of instances, only your email address will be shared.

Third Party Data & Data Comparisons: Under confidentiality agreements, beautytipshub.com may match user information with third party data. Also, beautytipshub.com discloses patterned user statistics in order to describe our services to prospective partners, advertisers, and or other third parties, and for other lawful purposes.

**5\. Third Party Advertising:**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. Our third-party advertising companies also separately places or recognizes a cookie file on your browser in the course of delivering advertisements to this website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit their respective privacy policies.
